Hey can you tell ceci we have academic team today if she wants to go?
Yeah
Do you think doing quizlets in practice is a good idea or use of time?  
Or do you think we should strongly encourage everyone or as many as possible to do it outside of practice since we can do that in our own time and then just do competitions in practice
The latter
THANK YOU
U R WELCOME
we should talk to him today maybe because I personally find it a waste of time and we can do them outside of practice and we can do competitions in matches
Yeah
Btw, cecilia can't come bc she has court but josie might
Ok cool
So should we try to do competition today bc I talked to him yesterday and idk why but I said I'm ok w the quizlets but maybe today we should just talk a little about why we can do them outside of class then we can maybe do a match or something
Like I'll talk w you at practice ever I feel like there's some material practice w math we could do in class but very little
I feel like the quizlets are something we need to do on our own time and practice should be reserved for something else
I just had a stroke reading that
Where tf is the punctuation
Also, i also feel like that
I know autocorrect on apple sucks
Also I don't care about punctuation in a text
You know Latin doesn't use punctuation so why must I?
Ur not in latin anymore tho, so all latin privileges are rescinded
Oh, also, did u give filer the microSD?
BRUH
Yeah he put it in a baggie and put it on a board I can show you after school bc I'm gonna go check on my scarf before academic team
bRuH
I'm being attacked ðŸ˜­
Ok thank you
Do you have Cecilia's phone number by any chance?
No I don't worry
*sorry
Can you come to academic team tomorrow
It's all good, and I'm not sure yet
Please comeeeeee i want there to be ppl
I'll try, how many people do we have?
If band ppl can go then it'll be like me, you, ceci, I am p sure Churchill is coming, and ceci's sister might go and maybe mckenna and possibly even Makenna
Im not coming today...sorry
Ok
Are you coming to astronomy night?
I'm too sick to
Oh god what's up?
Just a cold
Oh ok
Hey if we had academic team today could u go?
If enough people go then sure
Yay!  Church and I are gonna talk to him
I don't think he's here
That sucks
So we have academic team today, right?
Yes and we are gonna have at least 5 coming
It's definitely me, you, church, Makenna Prillaman, Jakob
And McKenna Shearer is probably coming
Hey can u do academic team Friday?
Yeah
As long as there are enough people, I'm good with Friday
Ok well church and I are def coming I can talk to Jakob and Makenna
So I'll def come to academic team today if you do.  Church will come as well.  I think even if it was us three it would still be a beneficial practice as we will all 3 likely be starters
But I leave early today so I just wanted to be sure bc I don't wanna come back and then have to leave lol
Sure, I'll come
Ok cool
hey so i'm assuming we are all still bringing food day stuff for tomorrow
yeah we are doing the food day today lmaoooo
idk why it autocorrected so many o's in lmao wtf
Cool, ill bring the stud
Studf
Stuff 
ok
Kroger doesn't have sprite cranberry what should i bring?
just get whatever
would u wanna go hitting?
mood af